<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Aboutme on Borna&#39;s Webpage</title>
    <link>https://borna-tl.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aboutme on Borna&#39;s Webpage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2023, Borna Tavasoli</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:43:07 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://borna-tl.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cv</title>
      <link>https://borna-tl.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 19:29:03 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borna-tl.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description> &lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; PDF Viewer </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aboutme</title>
      <link>https://borna-tl.github.io/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:43:07 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borna-tl.github.io/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>I am a last year undergraduate student studying computer engineering at university of tehran. My research interests include (but are not limited to 😊) algorithm design and complexity; I specially enjoy working on combinatorial optimization problems and working with discrete data structures. Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on algorithms with predictions for graph problems and the detour problem.
From July 2023 to October 2023, I was a research asisstant at SUFE under the supervision of B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://borna-tl.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 13:43:07 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://borna-tl.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I enjoy teaching very much. Infact, I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot of my undergraduate years teaching and learning how to teach. Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief description of my favorite contibutions:
- Algorithm Design 🧙‍♂️ Description: A challenging course covering essential algorithmic methods such as divide and conquer, dynamic programming, greedy algorithms, graph algorithms, network flow analysis, and the concept of NP problems. Role: Help design course material, organize the teaching staff, manage students’ activities, deliver lectures, and provid one-on-one guidance to students.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
